So I'm seeing folks commenting, you know, on Taraji's talking about, you know, how the equity in Hollywood is crazy.
Well, the lack of equity is crazy, especially for black women, et cetera, et cetera.
But I see people saying like, that's why y'all need to have your own.
You see, black actors need to stop asking for equity in a space that's all white.
Y'all need to get your own theaters, get your own lots.
Y'all need to.
OK, why do y'all think that everybody is an entrepreneur?
Why do y'all think that everybody has capital to even do that?
Why do y'all think that people are even down to work as your team to make that happen?
Baby, the math you mathin' ain't mathin'.
It's unmathable.
I just want to once and for all make it abundantly clear to everybody that like the arts is an art.
And the issue is not about why aren't black people putting on 50-11 hats to do some s**t.
The issue is that we shouldn't have to do that and we have to continue to press, OK?
We have to continue to press because the industry that exists has been in many ways been built on our backs.
So we can do multiple things at the same time.
We can be in independent spaces, but we can also demand our equity in the spaces that continuously use us.
And they even use our culture when we're not even there.
We can do that too.
I just think it's really disingenuous to suggest that everybody should be able to just build a moguldom, you know,
from the ground up when that really is an incredibly unique skill set that is very difficult to master.
And it also ignores the fact that, and I'm going to say the fact that,
black folks have still not mastered supporting each other.
I brought my show, Smart Funny and Black, to Tennessee for Juneteenth, to Nashville.
I gave two free shows to the city.
People snatched up the tickets in an hour.
And I had a third of the capacity there.
A third.
They wouldn't even support it when it was free, bro.
So I think we all need to get very real about what we are actually doing in party to what we're actually saying.
And also understanding that if you're really trying to support black folks,
it's going to actually be a bit more labor to do so because you're going to have to sift through and search through.
And it's going to cost more because independent black artists are not supported by studios.
So we have to charge more for things because it costs so much to do anything.
And we don't have the cushion that a studio has.
So I just want to provide this context, okay?
Because at the end of the day, Taraji P. Henson should be able to be the gifted actress that she is
and get paid her fair compensation without having to also be an executive producer, a producer, a hairstylist,
head of janitorial services, line producer, trombone player, and pedicurist on set.